Chapter #1
Great disovery!
"Kiteretsu Encyclopedia"
1903, December 11
In North Carolina, USA
For the very first time, Mankind succeeded in flight using engine-powered airplane.
All of you must very well know already that the Wright Brothers invented airplane, right?
Eiichi-san!
20 years before it, using glider a man leapt into the sky.
Otto Lilienthal, he's been said to flew in his glider around 2000 times.
Ah! Sir!
You can go out and pee.
There's a man who used glider, 32 years before Lilienthal.
You were paying attention to what I taught, Kite?
Tell us who's that, Kiteretsu!
Tell us.
Yes! Kite Kiteretsu Sai, a Japanese man.
Kiteretsu Sai?
Ansei year 6 or1859, From the top of a mountain, he flew for about 6 KM and surprised the villagers.
Care to explain to us, who is this Kiteretsu Sai?
Yes. He's my ancestor.
Don't sleep-talk about your dream.
But I mean it, sir.
Kiteretsu, maybe you should test what's wrong on your head.
There must be something wrong in your brain.
You'll know I was right...
Then are you going to fly in the sky?
Say what you want.
Ah! Miyo-chan!
Oh, Eiichi-san.
About my ancestor.
But you see, don't talk about it that much, with others.
Why?
Those who're not used to you, will be surprised.
Even you don't trust me, Miyo-chan?
That's not it. It's just that....
Naturally there should be records of him if he achieved such innovative feat.
You're right.
I'll research.
It'd be an great feat by today's standards.
Was it different in past?
For the crime of imitating birds, and creating a fuss,
He was arrested.
His work was burned
Thus Kiteretsu Sai wrote encyclopedias of his work.
That's absurd!
It was such a time.
I can relate to emotions of Kiteretsu Sai.
Things are still the same.
If only I had evidence, I could surprise everyone.
It's not that there's no evidence.
What is written in it?
Wow!
Huh?
There's nothing written in it.
He was arrested
This ain't an evidence.
Now that it come to this, only way to prove that I'm Kiteretsu Sai's descendant.
I just have to finish building this robot.
All done! Three weeks of hardship finally comes into fruit.
Now, I just have to press this switch to turn it on....
Success!
What was that for?!
How can you do that to your creator?
Stop!
Ei-chan!
What was all that about?
Don't!
Stop!
Oh no!
Ei-chan!
I wonder what this box contains.
It's very dusty.
Jinzuukyo?
So Kiteretsu Sai wore glasses, just like me.
Enough of rambling about ancestors! Studying is more important than inventions!
Then and now geniuses aren't recognised.